question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, "
                              "went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company "
                              "Facepunch Studios in March 2009.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Super Mario Bros. was released in 1990.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "'Undertale' is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Faust is a playable character in 'Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator'.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in 'Clash Royale'.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The game 'Battlefield 1' takes place during World War I.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "'Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater' takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the "
                              "destinies for two people forever.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 'Sonic Adventure', you are able to transform into "
                              "Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in "
                              "the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The 2005 video game 'Call of Duty 2: Big Red One' is not available on PC.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 'Undertale', the main character of the game is Sans.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In 'Call Of Duty: World At War', "
                              "the first appearance of the 'PPSH-41' in 'Zombies' "
                              "was in the map 'Der Riese'.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "'Sonic the Hedgehog 2' originally was going to have a time travel system.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In 'Minecraft', gold tools are faster than diamond tools.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the video game 'Splatoon', "
                              "the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The game 'Jetpack Joyride' was created by 'Redbrick Studios'.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
                 ]
